<?xml version="1.0" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE entity PUBLIC "-//UC Berkeley//DTD MoML 1//EN"
    "http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/xml/dtd/MoML_1.dtd">
<entity name="Ligand_Parameterization_Series" class="org.kepler.moml.CompositeClassEntity">
    <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:54185:3087:8">
    </property>
    <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="org.kepler.moml.CompositeClassEntity">
        <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="null">
        </property>
    </property>
    <property name="_createdBy" class="ptolemy.kernel.attributes.VersionAttribute" value="9.1.devel">
    </property>
    <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:24556:9:109:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:50:10:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:54:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:56:422:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:106:6:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:107:60:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:141:52:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:761:164:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:976:212:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:60:62">
    </property>
    <property name="SDF Director" class="ptolemy.domains.sdf.kernel.SDFDirector">
        <property name="iterations" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="1">
        </property>
        <property name="vectorizationFactor" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="1">
        </property>
        <property name="allowDisconnectedGraphs" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
        </property>
        <property name="allowRateChanges" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
        </property>
        <property name="constrainBufferSizes" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="period" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="0.0">
        </property>
        <property name="synchronizeToRealTime" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
        </property>
        <property name="Scheduler" class="ptolemy.domains.sdf.kernel.SDFScheduler">
            <property name="constrainBufferSizes" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="constrainBufferSizes">
            </property>
        </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;&lt;p&gt;The SDF Director is often used to oversee fairly simple, sequential workflows in which the director can determine the order of actor invocation from the workflow. Types of workflows that would run well under an SDF Director include processing and reformatting tabular data, converting one data type to another, and reading and plotting a series of data points. A workflow in which an image is read, processed (rotated, scaled, clipped, filtered, etc.), and then displayed, is also an example of a sequential workflow that requires a director simply to ensure that each actor fires in the proper order (i.e., that each actor executes only after it receives its required inputs).&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The SDF Director is very efficient and will not tax system resources with overhead. However, this efficiency requires that certain conditions be met, namely that the data consumption and production rate of each actor in an SDF workflow be constant and declared. If an actor reads one piece of data and calculates and outputs a single result, it must always read and output a single token of data. This data rate cannot change during workflow execution and, in general, workflows that require dynamic scheduling and/or flow control cannot use this director. Additionally, the SDF Director has no understanding of passing time (at least by default), and actors that depend on a notion of time may not work as expected. For example, a TimedPlotter actor will plot all values at time zero when used in SDF. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;By default, the SDF Director requires that all actors in its workflow be connected. Otherwise, the director cannot account for concurrency between disconnected workflow parts. Usually, a PN Director should be used for workflows that contain disconnected actors; however, the SDF Director's allowDisconnectedGraphs parameter may also be set to true. The SDF Director will then schedule each disconnected &quot;island&quot; independently. The director cannot infer the sequential relationship between disconnected actors (i.e., nothing forces the director to finish executing all actors on one island before firing actors on another). However, the order of execution within each island should be correct. Usually, disconnected graphs in an SDF model indicate an error.&lt;/p&gt;&#10; &#10;&lt;p&gt;Because SDF Directors schedule actors to fire only after they receive their inputs, workflows that require loops (feeding an actor's output back into its input port for further processing) can cause &quot;deadlock&quot; errors. The deadlock errors occur because the actor depends on its own output value as an initial input. To fix this problem, use a SampleDelay actor to generate and inject an initial input value into the workflow.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The SDF Director determines the order in which actors execute and how many times each actor needs to be fired to complete a single iteration of the workflow. This schedule is calculated BEFORE the director begins to iterate the workflow. Because the SDF Director calculates a schedule in advance, it is quite efficient. However, SDF workflows must be static. In other words, the same number of tokens must be consumed/produced at every iteration of the workflow. Workflows that require dynamic control structures, such as a BooleanSwitch actor that sends output on one of two ports depending on the value of a 'control', cannot be used with an SDF Director because the number of tokens on each output can change for each execution.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Unless otherwise specified, the SDF Director assumes that each actor consumes and produces exactly one token per channel on each firing. Actors that do not follow the one-token-per-channel firing convention (e.g., Repeat or Ramp) must declare the number of tokens they produce or consume via the appropriate parameters. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The number of times a workflow is iterated is controlled by the director's iterations parameter. By default, this parameter is set to &quot;0&quot;. Note that &quot;0&quot; does not mean &quot;no iterations.&quot; Rather, &quot;0&quot; means that the workflow will iterate forever. Values greater than zero specify the actual number of times the director should execute the entire workflow. A value of 1, meaning that the director will run the workflow once, is often the best setting when building an SDF workflow. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The amount of data processed by an SDF workflow is a function of both the number of times the workflow iterates and the value of the director's vectorizationFactor parameter. The vectorizationFactor is used to increase the efficiency of a workflow by increasing the number of times actors fire each time the workflow iterates. If the parameter is set to a positive integer (other than 1), the director will fire each actor the specified number of times more than normal. The default is 1, indicating that no vectorization should be performed. Keep in mind that changing the vectorizationFactor parameter changes the meaning of a nested SDF workflow and may cause deadlock in a workflow that uses it. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The SDF Director has several advanced parameters that are generally only relevant when an SDF workflow contains composite components. In most cases the period, timeResolution, synchronizeToRealTime, allowRateChanges, timeResolution, and constrainBufferSizes parameters can be left at their default values.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;For more information about the SDF Director, see the Ptolemy documentation (http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/papers/05/ptIIdesign3-domains/ptIIdesign3-domains.pdf).&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:allowDisconnectedGraphs" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether to allow disconnected actors in the workflow (by default, all actors are required to be connected). If disconnected actors are permitted, the SDF Director will schedule each disconnected 'island' independently. Nothing &quot;forces&quot; the director to finish executing all actors on one island before firing actors on another. However, the order of execution within each island should be correct. Usually, disconnected graphs in an SDF workflow indicate an error.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:allowRateChanges" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether dynamic rate changes are permitted or not. By default, rate changes are not permitted, and the director will perform a check to disallow such workflows. If the parameter is selected, then workflows that require rate parameters to be modified during execution are valid, and the SDF Director will dynamically compute a new schedule at runtime. This is an advanced parameter that can usually be left at its default value.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:timeResolution" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The time precision used by this director. All time values are rounded to the nearest multiple of this number. The value is a double that defaults to &quot;1E-10&quot; (which is 10-10). This is an advanced parameter that can usually be left at its default value.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:constrainBufferSizes" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether buffer sizes are fixed. By default, buffers are fixed, and attempts to write to the buffer that cause the buffer to exceed its scheduled size result in an error. This is an advanced parameter that can usually be left at its default value.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:iterations" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify the number of times a workflow is iterated. By default, this parameter is set to &quot;0&quot;. Note that &quot;0&quot; does not mean &quot;no iterations.&quot; Rather, &quot;0&quot; means that the workflow will iterate forever. Values greater than zero specify the actual number of times the director should execute the entire workflow. A value of 1, meaning that the director will run the workflow once, is often the best setting when building an SDF workflow. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:vectorizationFactor" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The vectorizationFactor is used to increase the efficiency of a workflow by increasing the number of times actors fire each time the workflow iterates. If the parameter is set to a positive integer (other than 1), the director will fire each actor the specified number of times more than normal. The default is 1, indicating that no vectorization should be performed. Keep in mind that changing the vectorizationFactor parameter changes the meaning of a nested SDF workflow and may cause deadlock in a workflow that uses it. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:synchronizeToRealTime" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether the execution should synchronize to real time or not. By default, the director does not synchronize to real time. If synchronize is selected, the director will only process the workflow when elapsed real time matches the product of the period parameter and the iteration count. Note: if the period parameter has a value of 0.0 (the default), then selecting this parameter has no effect. This is an advanced parameter that can usually be left at its default value.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:period" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The time period of each iteration. The value is a double that defaults to 0.0, which means that the director does not increment workflow time. If the value greater than 0.0, the actor will increment workflow time each time it fires. This is an advanced parameter that can usually be left at its default value. </configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:24556:40:1">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.domains.sdf.kernel.SDFDirector">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:directorclass:1:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#Director">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#Director">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[595.0, 75.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:director:1:1">
        </property>
    </property>
    <property name="_windowProperties" class="ptolemy.actor.gui.WindowPropertiesAttribute" value="{bounds={1918, 0, 1924, 1084}, maximized=true}">
    </property>
    <property name="_vergilSize" class="ptolemy.actor.gui.SizeAttribute" value="[1600, 909]">
    </property>
    <property name="_vergilZoomFactor" class="ptolemy.data.expr.ExpertParameter" value="1.2500000000000004">
    </property>
    <property name="_vergilCenter" class="ptolemy.data.expr.ExpertParameter" value="{761.6, 318.6000000000003}">
    </property>
    <property name="c" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="0">
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Neil Smyth, Edward A. Lee, Xiaojun Liu</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>$Id: Parameter.xml 30507 2012-08-22 23:51:26Z crawl $</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;&lt;p&gt;Parameter extends Variable with additional support for string-valued&#10; variables that makes these friendlier at the user interface level.&#10; In particular, this class supports an annotation that specifies&#10; choices for values.  A user interface can use this to present a&#10; choice dialog that offers the specified values.  This is typically&#10; used when a particular set of choices make sense.  The values can&#10; be any expression, or if used in conjunction with string mode,&#10; any string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10; &lt;p&gt;&#10; By default, an instance of Parameter, unlike Variable, is persistent.&lt;/p&gt;&#10; &lt;p&gt;&#10; By convention, an instance of NamedObj has a set of attributes,&#10; some of which are visible to users and some of which are not.&#10; When a user interface presents these attributes&#10; for editing, it presents only those that are visible.&#10; By default, an instance of Parameter is visible, as indicated by the fact&#10; that it returns FULL in its getVisibility() method.  This can be overridden&#10; by calling setVisibility().&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:974:1">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:1184:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="_hideName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonAttribute">
        </property>
        <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.ValueIcon">
            <property name="_color" class="ptolemy.actor.gui.ColorAttribute" value="{0.0, 0.0, 1.0, 1.0}">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="_smallIconDescription" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonConfigurableAttribute">
            <configure>
      <svg>
        <text x="20" style="font-size:14; font-family:SansSerif; fill:blue" y="20">-P-</text>
      </svg>
    </configure>
        </property>
        <property name="_editorFactory" class="ptolemy.vergil.toolbox.VisibleParameterEditorFactory">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[325.0, 130.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:420:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:137:1">
        </property>
    </property>
    <property name="l" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="DM0">
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Edward A. Lee</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;StringParameter specifies a persistent string. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Change the name of the StringParameter to better identify the specified value (right-click the parameter and select &quot;Customize Name&quot; from the menu). Other actors may refer to the StringParameter using the $NAME syntax (e.g. $Parameter).&#10;&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:975:1">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:1185:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="_hideName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonAttribute">
        </property>
        <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.ValueIcon">
            <property name="_color" class="ptolemy.actor.gui.ColorAttribute" value="{1.0, 0.0, 0.0, 1.0}">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="_smallIconDescription" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonConfigurableAttribute">
            <configure>
        <svg>
          <text x="20" style="font-size:14; font-family:SansSerif; fill:red" y="20">-S-</text>
        </svg>
      </configure>
        </property>
        <property name="_editorFactory" class="ptolemy.vergil.toolbox.VisibleParameterEditorFactory">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[325.0, 150.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:421:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:142:1">
        </property>
    </property>
    <property name="d" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="/home/pieong/Desktop/git/workflows-master/LigandParameterizationSerial/input">
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Edward A. Lee</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;StringParameter specifies a persistent string. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Change the name of the StringParameter to better identify the specified value (right-click the parameter and select &quot;Customize Name&quot; from the menu). Other actors may refer to the StringParameter using the $NAME syntax (e.g. $Parameter).&#10;&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:774:2">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:1185:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="_hideName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonAttribute">
        </property>
        <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.ValueIcon">
            <property name="_color" class="ptolemy.actor.gui.ColorAttribute" value="{1.0, 0.0, 0.0, 1.0}">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="_smallIconDescription" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonConfigurableAttribute">
            <configure>
        <svg>
          <text x="20" style="font-size:14; font-family:SansSerif; fill:red" y="20">-S-</text>
        </svg>
      </configure>
        </property>
        <property name="_editorFactory" class="ptolemy.vergil.toolbox.VisibleParameterEditorFactory">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[325.0, 170.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:421:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:142:1">
        </property>
    </property>
    <property name="n" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="12">
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Neil Smyth, Edward A. Lee, Xiaojun Liu</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>$Id: Parameter.xml 30507 2012-08-22 23:51:26Z crawl $</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;&lt;p&gt;Parameter extends Variable with additional support for string-valued&#10; variables that makes these friendlier at the user interface level.&#10; In particular, this class supports an annotation that specifies&#10; choices for values.  A user interface can use this to present a&#10; choice dialog that offers the specified values.  This is typically&#10; used when a particular set of choices make sense.  The values can&#10; be any expression, or if used in conjunction with string mode,&#10; any string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10; &lt;p&gt;&#10; By default, an instance of Parameter, unlike Variable, is persistent.&lt;/p&gt;&#10; &lt;p&gt;&#10; By convention, an instance of NamedObj has a set of attributes,&#10; some of which are visible to users and some of which are not.&#10; When a user interface presents these attributes&#10; for editing, it presents only those that are visible.&#10; By default, an instance of Parameter is visible, as indicated by the fact&#10; that it returns FULL in its getVisibility() method.  This can be overridden&#10; by calling setVisibility().&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:119:1">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:1184:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="_hideName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonAttribute">
        </property>
        <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.ValueIcon">
            <property name="_color" class="ptolemy.actor.gui.ColorAttribute" value="{0.0, 0.0, 1.0, 1.0}">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="_smallIconDescription" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonConfigurableAttribute">
            <configure>
      <svg>
        <text x="20" style="font-size:14; font-family:SansSerif; fill:blue" y="20">-P-</text>
      </svg>
    </configure>
        </property>
        <property name="_editorFactory" class="ptolemy.vergil.toolbox.VisibleParameterEditorFactory">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[790.0, 135.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:420:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:137:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:974:1">
        </property>
    </property>
    <property name="m" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="96">
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Neil Smyth, Edward A. Lee, Xiaojun Liu</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>$Id: Parameter.xml 30507 2012-08-22 23:51:26Z crawl $</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;&lt;p&gt;Parameter extends Variable with additional support for string-valued&#10; variables that makes these friendlier at the user interface level.&#10; In particular, this class supports an annotation that specifies&#10; choices for values.  A user interface can use this to present a&#10; choice dialog that offers the specified values.  This is typically&#10; used when a particular set of choices make sense.  The values can&#10; be any expression, or if used in conjunction with string mode,&#10; any string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10; &lt;p&gt;&#10; By default, an instance of Parameter, unlike Variable, is persistent.&lt;/p&gt;&#10; &lt;p&gt;&#10; By convention, an instance of NamedObj has a set of attributes,&#10; some of which are visible to users and some of which are not.&#10; When a user interface presents these attributes&#10; for editing, it presents only those that are visible.&#10; By default, an instance of Parameter is visible, as indicated by the fact&#10; that it returns FULL in its getVisibility() method.  This can be overridden&#10; by calling setVisibility().&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:119:2">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:1184:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#Parameter">
        </property>
        <property name="_hideName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonAttribute">
        </property>
        <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.ValueIcon">
            <property name="_color" class="ptolemy.actor.gui.ColorAttribute" value="{0.0, 0.0, 1.0, 1.0}">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="_smallIconDescription" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.SingletonConfigurableAttribute">
            <configure>
      <svg>
        <text x="20" style="font-size:14; font-family:SansSerif; fill:blue" y="20">-P-</text>
      </svg>
    </configure>
        </property>
        <property name="_editorFactory" class="ptolemy.vergil.toolbox.VisibleParameterEditorFactory">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[790.0, 155.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:420:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:137:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:974:1">
        </property>
    </property>
    <entity name="Tleap" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
        <property name="NONE" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="0">
        </property>
        <property name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="&quot;tleap -f tleap_savepdb.script&quot;">
        </property>
        <property name="directory" class="ptolemy.data.expr.FileParameter" value="$d">
            <property name="allowFiles" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
            <property name="allowDirectories" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="environment" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="{{name = &quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}">
        </property>
        <property name="ignoreIOExceptionReadErrors" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
        </property>
        <property name="prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="1">
        </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Xiaojun Liu, Edward A. Lee, Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor executes a system command from a workflow. The actor accepts a command, a directory and environment in which to execute the command, and a command input string. Once the command has finished executing, the actor will output the execution results along with any errors. If no results are generated, the actor will output an empty string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor depends on system-specific executables and is operating-system specific.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;To mimic the effect of executing a command in a shell interpreter, set the command parameter to &quot;cmd&quot; (Windows) or &quot;sh&quot; (Windows with Cygwin or Linux), and then provide commands, as a string, via the input port. Note that each passed command must be terminated with a newline. For example, to open a workflow in vergil and run it, set command to &quot;sh&quot; and use a StringConstant actor to pass the  input port the string: &#10; &quot;vergil -run model.xml\n exit\n&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts data generated by the executed command, output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the command generates no data on standard out, then the empty string (a string of length zero) is generated. </configure></property>
<property name="port:input" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An input port that accepts strings to pass to the standard input of the subprocess. Note that a newline is not appended to the string. If you require a newline, add one using the AddSubtract actor. This port is an input port of type String.</configure></property>
<property name="port:error" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts any errors generated by the command execution. Errors are output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the execution generates no errors, an empty string is output. </configure></property>
<property name="port:trigger" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If connected, a token must be available on this port before actor will execute.</configure></property>
<property name="port:exitCode" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the command's exit code. A non-zero value signifies an error.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:environment" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An array of records that name an environment variable and a value:&#10; &#10;  {{name = &quot;NAME1&quot;, value = &quot;value1&quot;}...}&#10;  &#10;Where NAME1 is the name of the environment variable, and value1 is the value. &#10;For example, {{name = &quot;PTII&quot;, value = &quot;c:/ptII&quot;}} would set the value of the PTII to c:/ptII. &#10;If the parameter is set to {{name=&quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}, then the environment from the parent process is used. If environmental variables are set with the parameter, the parent values may not be passed to the process. To view the current environment, use the &quot;env&quot; command.&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:directory" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The directory in which to execute the command. The default value of this parameter $CWD, which represents the user's current working or home directory. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then throw an exception if the subprocess returns non-zero.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If a positive integer, then it is the maximum number of times to execute the actor.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;If true, then prepend the platform dependent shell command to the&#10;parsed value of the command parameter.  By setting this argument&#10;to true, it is possible to invoke commands in a platform neutral&#10;method.&#10;&lt;p&gt;Under Windows NT or XP, the arguments &quot;cmd.exe&quot; and &quot;/C&quot; are&#10;prepended.  Under Windows 95, the arguments &quot;command.com&quot; and &quot;/C&quot;&#10;are prepended.  Under all other platforms, the arguments &quot;/bin/sh&quot;&#10;and &quot;-c&quot; are prepended. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The default value of this parameter is a boolean of value false,&#10;which allows the user to arbitrarily invoke /bin/sh scripts on all&#10;platforms. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; This must be true if file redirection is used in &lt;i&gt;command&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; Under Cygwin, if true, the path environment of the subprocess is not&#10;identical to the path of the calling process. In this case the full path to the program&#10;must be specified.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then actor will wait until subprocess completes.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:command" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The command to be executed (e.g., echo &quot;Hello, world.&quot;). The command can be specified via either the command port or parameter.</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:768:18">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:976:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#ExternalExecutionEnvironmentActor">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#UnixCommand">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[1110.0, 210.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:102:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:139:5">
        </property>
        <port name="output" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="trigger" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="multiport"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="error" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="input" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="exitCode" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
    </entity>
    <entity name="String Constant" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.StringConst">
        <property name="value" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="source leaprc.ff99SB&#10;source  leaprc.gaff&#10;loadAmberPrep $l.prepc&#10;loadAmberParams $l.frcmod&#10;c=MOL&#10;savepdb c $l-new.pdb&#10;quit">
            <property name="style" class="ptolemy.actor.gui.style.TextStyle">
                <property name="height" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="10">
                </property>
                <property name="width" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="30">
                </property>
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="1">
        </property>
        <property name="NONE" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="0">
        </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Edward Lee</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The StringConstant actor outputs a string specified via the actor's value parameter.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Specifying strings with the StringConstant actor is convenient, as the actor does not require that strings be surrounded by quotes. The actor is often used to specify file paths, which can be selected using the Browse button available in the actor's parameters.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Specified string values can include references to parameters within scope (i.e., parameters defined at the same level of the hierarchy or higher). &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;NOTE: If using a PN Director, the 'firingCountLimit' parameter is often set to a finite integer (e.g. '1') so that the workflow will terminate. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts a string constant specified by the value parameter.  </configure></property>
<property name="port:trigger" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A multiport that has no declared type (in other words, the port can accept any data type: double, int, array, etc.) If the port is connected, the actor will not fire until the trigger port receives an input token. Connecting the port is optional, but useful when scheduling the actor to perform at a certain time. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The limit on the number of times the actor will fire. The default value is 'NONE', meaning there is no limit on the number of time the constant will be provided to the output port. Any integer can be provided as a value for this parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:value" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The value produced by the actor. Specified strings do not require enclosing quotes. (To include a '$' sign in the string, enter '$$'.)</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:54185:3090:1">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.StringConst">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:1052:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#StringFunctionActor">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#Constant">
        </property>
        <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.BoxedValueIcon">
            <property name="attributeName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="value">
            </property>
            <property name="displayWidth" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="60">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[790.0, 320.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:204:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:762:19">
        </property>
        <port name="trigger" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="multiport"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
    </entity>
    <entity name="File Writer" class="org.geon.FileWrite">
        <property name="fileName" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.FilePortParameter" value="$d/tleap_savepdb.script">
        </property>
        <property name="append" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
        </property>
        <property name="confirmOverwrite" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="alwaysFlush" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>No author given</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The FileWriter actor reads a string and writes it to a file. The actor outputs the file path of the generated file.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Specify a destination file path with the fileName parameter. If the specified file does not exist, then the actor will create it.  If the file already exists, then the actor will ask for permission to overwrite it (unless the append parameter is selected, in which case the new content is appended to the existing content).&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The actor is similar to the LineWriter, except that the FileWriter outputs the generated file path, while the LineWriter actor does not. FileWriter is also similar to TextFileWriter, except that the FileWriter actor adds line breaks, while the TextFileWriter does not.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:input" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An input port that receives a string to write to a file.</configure></property>
<property name="port:url" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the file name of the generated file.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:append" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether to append the input string to an existing, specified file. By default, the actor will overwrite any preexisting file.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:confirmOverwrite" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether the actor should confirm before overwriting an existing file. By default, the actor will ask for confirmation.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:fileName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The name of the file to which to write. See FileParameter for more information about specifying file names. </configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:767:26">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="org.geon.FileWrite">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:1003:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#WriterOutputActor">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#LocalOutput">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[925.0, 310.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:144:1">
        </property>
        <port name="input" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="multiport"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="fileName" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
    </entity>
    <entity name="FRCMOD" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
        <property name="NONE" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="0">
        </property>
        <property name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="&quot;parmchk -i $l.prepc -f prepc -o $l.frcmod&quot;">
        </property>
        <property name="directory" class="ptolemy.data.expr.FileParameter" value="$d">
            <property name="allowFiles" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
            <property name="allowDirectories" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="environment" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="{{name = &quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}">
        </property>
        <property name="ignoreIOExceptionReadErrors" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
        </property>
        <property name="prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="1">
        </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Xiaojun Liu, Edward A. Lee, Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor executes a system command from a workflow. The actor accepts a command, a directory and environment in which to execute the command, and a command input string. Once the command has finished executing, the actor will output the execution results along with any errors. If no results are generated, the actor will output an empty string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor depends on system-specific executables and is operating-system specific.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;To mimic the effect of executing a command in a shell interpreter, set the command parameter to &quot;cmd&quot; (Windows) or &quot;sh&quot; (Windows with Cygwin or Linux), and then provide commands, as a string, via the input port. Note that each passed command must be terminated with a newline. For example, to open a workflow in vergil and run it, set command to &quot;sh&quot; and use a StringConstant actor to pass the  input port the string: &#10; &quot;vergil -run model.xml\n exit\n&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:input" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An input port that accepts strings to pass to the standard input of the subprocess. Note that a newline is not appended to the string. If you require a newline, add one using the AddSubtract actor. This port is an input port of type String.</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts data generated by the executed command, output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the command generates no data on standard out, then the empty string (a string of length zero) is generated. </configure></property>
<property name="port:trigger" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If connected, a token must be available on this port before actor will execute.</configure></property>
<property name="port:error" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts any errors generated by the command execution. Errors are output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the execution generates no errors, an empty string is output. </configure></property>
<property name="port:exitCode" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the command's exit code. A non-zero value signifies an error.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:environment" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An array of records that name an environment variable and a value:&#10; &#10;  {{name = &quot;NAME1&quot;, value = &quot;value1&quot;}...}&#10;  &#10;Where NAME1 is the name of the environment variable, and value1 is the value. &#10;For example, {{name = &quot;PTII&quot;, value = &quot;c:/ptII&quot;}} would set the value of the PTII to c:/ptII. &#10;If the parameter is set to {{name=&quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}, then the environment from the parent process is used. If environmental variables are set with the parameter, the parent values may not be passed to the process. To view the current environment, use the &quot;env&quot; command.&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:directory" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The directory in which to execute the command. The default value of this parameter $CWD, which represents the user's current working or home directory. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then throw an exception if the subprocess returns non-zero.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If a positive integer, then it is the maximum number of times to execute the actor.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;If true, then prepend the platform dependent shell command to the&#10;parsed value of the command parameter.  By setting this argument&#10;to true, it is possible to invoke commands in a platform neutral&#10;method.&#10;&lt;p&gt;Under Windows NT or XP, the arguments &quot;cmd.exe&quot; and &quot;/C&quot; are&#10;prepended.  Under Windows 95, the arguments &quot;command.com&quot; and &quot;/C&quot;&#10;are prepended.  Under all other platforms, the arguments &quot;/bin/sh&quot;&#10;and &quot;-c&quot; are prepended. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The default value of this parameter is a boolean of value false,&#10;which allows the user to arbitrarily invoke /bin/sh scripts on all&#10;platforms. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; This must be true if file redirection is used in &lt;i&gt;command&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; Under Cygwin, if true, the path environment of the subprocess is not&#10;identical to the path of the calling process. In this case the full path to the program&#10;must be specified.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then actor will wait until subprocess completes.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:command" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The command to be executed (e.g., echo &quot;Hello, world.&quot;). The command can be specified via either the command port or parameter.</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:778:37">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:976:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#ExternalExecutionEnvironmentActor">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#UnixCommand">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[920.0, 215.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:102:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:138:10">
        </property>
        <port name="output" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="trigger" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="multiport"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="error" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="input" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="exitCode" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
    </entity>
    <entity name="Gaussian Log File" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
        <property name="NONE" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="0">
        </property>
        <property name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="&quot;g09 &lt; $l.inp &gt; $l.log&quot;">
        </property>
        <property name="directory" class="ptolemy.data.expr.FileParameter" value="$d">
            <property name="allowFiles" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
            <property name="allowDirectories" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="environment" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="{{name = &quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}">
        </property>
        <property name="ignoreIOExceptionReadErrors" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
        </property>
        <property name="prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="1">
        </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Xiaojun Liu, Edward A. Lee, Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor executes a system command from a workflow. The actor accepts a command, a directory and environment in which to execute the command, and a command input string. Once the command has finished executing, the actor will output the execution results along with any errors. If no results are generated, the actor will output an empty string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor depends on system-specific executables and is operating-system specific.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;To mimic the effect of executing a command in a shell interpreter, set the command parameter to &quot;cmd&quot; (Windows) or &quot;sh&quot; (Windows with Cygwin or Linux), and then provide commands, as a string, via the input port. Note that each passed command must be terminated with a newline. For example, to open a workflow in vergil and run it, set command to &quot;sh&quot; and use a StringConstant actor to pass the  input port the string: &#10; &quot;vergil -run model.xml\n exit\n&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts data generated by the executed command, output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the command generates no data on standard out, then the empty string (a string of length zero) is generated. </configure></property>
<property name="port:input" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An input port that accepts strings to pass to the standard input of the subprocess. Note that a newline is not appended to the string. If you require a newline, add one using the AddSubtract actor. This port is an input port of type String.</configure></property>
<property name="port:error" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts any errors generated by the command execution. Errors are output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the execution generates no errors, an empty string is output. </configure></property>
<property name="port:trigger" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If connected, a token must be available on this port before actor will execute.</configure></property>
<property name="port:exitCode" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the command's exit code. A non-zero value signifies an error.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:environment" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An array of records that name an environment variable and a value:&#10; &#10;  {{name = &quot;NAME1&quot;, value = &quot;value1&quot;}...}&#10;  &#10;Where NAME1 is the name of the environment variable, and value1 is the value. &#10;For example, {{name = &quot;PTII&quot;, value = &quot;c:/ptII&quot;}} would set the value of the PTII to c:/ptII. &#10;If the parameter is set to {{name=&quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}, then the environment from the parent process is used. If environmental variables are set with the parameter, the parent values may not be passed to the process. To view the current environment, use the &quot;env&quot; command.&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:directory" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The directory in which to execute the command. The default value of this parameter $CWD, which represents the user's current working or home directory. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then throw an exception if the subprocess returns non-zero.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If a positive integer, then it is the maximum number of times to execute the actor.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;If true, then prepend the platform dependent shell command to the&#10;parsed value of the command parameter.  By setting this argument&#10;to true, it is possible to invoke commands in a platform neutral&#10;method.&#10;&lt;p&gt;Under Windows NT or XP, the arguments &quot;cmd.exe&quot; and &quot;/C&quot; are&#10;prepended.  Under Windows 95, the arguments &quot;command.com&quot; and &quot;/C&quot;&#10;are prepended.  Under all other platforms, the arguments &quot;/bin/sh&quot;&#10;and &quot;-c&quot; are prepended. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The default value of this parameter is a boolean of value false,&#10;which allows the user to arbitrarily invoke /bin/sh scripts on all&#10;platforms. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; This must be true if file redirection is used in &lt;i&gt;command&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; Under Cygwin, if true, the path environment of the subprocess is not&#10;identical to the path of the calling process. In this case the full path to the program&#10;must be specified.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then actor will wait until subprocess completes.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:command" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The command to be executed (e.g., echo &quot;Hello, world.&quot;). The command can be specified via either the command port or parameter.</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:775:1">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:976:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#ExternalExecutionEnvironmentActor">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#UnixCommand">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[575.0, 220.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:102:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:64:12">
        </property>
        <port name="output" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="trigger" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="multiport"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="error" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="input" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="exitCode" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
    </entity>
    <entity name="Antechamber2" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
        <property name="NONE" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="0">
        </property>
        <property name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="&quot;antechamber -i $l.gesp -fi gesp -o $l.prepc -fo prepc -c resp -eq 1 -at gaff -nc $c&quot;">
        </property>
        <property name="directory" class="ptolemy.data.expr.FileParameter" value="$d">
            <property name="allowFiles" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
            <property name="allowDirectories" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="environment" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="{{name = &quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}">
        </property>
        <property name="ignoreIOExceptionReadErrors" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
        </property>
        <property name="prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="1">
        </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Xiaojun Liu, Edward A. Lee, Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor executes a system command from a workflow. The actor accepts a command, a directory and environment in which to execute the command, and a command input string. Once the command has finished executing, the actor will output the execution results along with any errors. If no results are generated, the actor will output an empty string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor depends on system-specific executables and is operating-system specific.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;To mimic the effect of executing a command in a shell interpreter, set the command parameter to &quot;cmd&quot; (Windows) or &quot;sh&quot; (Windows with Cygwin or Linux), and then provide commands, as a string, via the input port. Note that each passed command must be terminated with a newline. For example, to open a workflow in vergil and run it, set command to &quot;sh&quot; and use a StringConstant actor to pass the  input port the string: &#10; &quot;vergil -run model.xml\n exit\n&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts data generated by the executed command, output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the command generates no data on standard out, then the empty string (a string of length zero) is generated. </configure></property>
<property name="port:input" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An input port that accepts strings to pass to the standard input of the subprocess. Note that a newline is not appended to the string. If you require a newline, add one using the AddSubtract actor. This port is an input port of type String.</configure></property>
<property name="port:error" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts any errors generated by the command execution. Errors are output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the execution generates no errors, an empty string is output. </configure></property>
<property name="port:trigger" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If connected, a token must be available on this port before actor will execute.</configure></property>
<property name="port:exitCode" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the command's exit code. A non-zero value signifies an error.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:environment" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An array of records that name an environment variable and a value:&#10; &#10;  {{name = &quot;NAME1&quot;, value = &quot;value1&quot;}...}&#10;  &#10;Where NAME1 is the name of the environment variable, and value1 is the value. &#10;For example, {{name = &quot;PTII&quot;, value = &quot;c:/ptII&quot;}} would set the value of the PTII to c:/ptII. &#10;If the parameter is set to {{name=&quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}, then the environment from the parent process is used. If environmental variables are set with the parameter, the parent values may not be passed to the process. To view the current environment, use the &quot;env&quot; command.&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:directory" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The directory in which to execute the command. The default value of this parameter $CWD, which represents the user's current working or home directory. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then throw an exception if the subprocess returns non-zero.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If a positive integer, then it is the maximum number of times to execute the actor.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;If true, then prepend the platform dependent shell command to the&#10;parsed value of the command parameter.  By setting this argument&#10;to true, it is possible to invoke commands in a platform neutral&#10;method.&#10;&lt;p&gt;Under Windows NT or XP, the arguments &quot;cmd.exe&quot; and &quot;/C&quot; are&#10;prepended.  Under Windows 95, the arguments &quot;command.com&quot; and &quot;/C&quot;&#10;are prepended.  Under all other platforms, the arguments &quot;/bin/sh&quot;&#10;and &quot;-c&quot; are prepended. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The default value of this parameter is a boolean of value false,&#10;which allows the user to arbitrarily invoke /bin/sh scripts on all&#10;platforms. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; This must be true if file redirection is used in &lt;i&gt;command&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; Under Cygwin, if true, the path environment of the subprocess is not&#10;identical to the path of the calling process. In this case the full path to the program&#10;must be specified.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then actor will wait until subprocess completes.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:command" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The command to be executed (e.g., echo &quot;Hello, world.&quot;). The command can be specified via either the command port or parameter.</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:777:55">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:976:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#ExternalExecutionEnvironmentActor">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#UnixCommand">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[745.0, 220.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:102:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:68:14">
        </property>
        <port name="output" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="trigger" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="multiport"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="error" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="input" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="exitCode" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
    </entity>
    <entity name="Antechamber1" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
        <property name="NONE" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="0">
        </property>
        <property name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="&quot;antechamber -i $l.pdb -fi pdb -o $l.inp -fo gcrt -gv 1 -ge $l.gesp -nc $c&quot;">
        </property>
        <property name="directory" class="ptolemy.data.expr.FileParameter" value="$d">
            <property name="allowFiles" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
            <property name="allowDirectories" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="environment" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="{{name = &quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}">
        </property>
        <property name="ignoreIOExceptionReadErrors" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
        </property>
        <property name="prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
        </property>
        <property name="firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="1">
        </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Xiaojun Liu, Edward A. Lee, Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor executes a system command from a workflow. The actor accepts a command, a directory and environment in which to execute the command, and a command input string. Once the command has finished executing, the actor will output the execution results along with any errors. If no results are generated, the actor will output an empty string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The External Execution actor depends on system-specific executables and is operating-system specific.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;To mimic the effect of executing a command in a shell interpreter, set the command parameter to &quot;cmd&quot; (Windows) or &quot;sh&quot; (Windows with Cygwin or Linux), and then provide commands, as a string, via the input port. Note that each passed command must be terminated with a newline. For example, to open a workflow in vergil and run it, set command to &quot;sh&quot; and use a StringConstant actor to pass the  input port the string: &#10; &quot;vergil -run model.xml\n exit\n&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts data generated by the executed command, output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the command generates no data on standard out, then the empty string (a string of length zero) is generated. </configure></property>
<property name="port:input" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An input port that accepts strings to pass to the standard input of the subprocess. Note that a newline is not appended to the string. If you require a newline, add one using the AddSubtract actor. This port is an input port of type String.</configure></property>
<property name="port:error" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts any errors generated by the command execution. Errors are output as a string after the command has finished executing. If the execution generates no errors, an empty string is output. </configure></property>
<property name="port:trigger" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If connected, a token must be available on this port before actor will execute.</configure></property>
<property name="port:exitCode" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the command's exit code. A non-zero value signifies an error.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:environment" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An array of records that name an environment variable and a value:&#10; &#10;  {{name = &quot;NAME1&quot;, value = &quot;value1&quot;}...}&#10;  &#10;Where NAME1 is the name of the environment variable, and value1 is the value. &#10;For example, {{name = &quot;PTII&quot;, value = &quot;c:/ptII&quot;}} would set the value of the PTII to c:/ptII. &#10;If the parameter is set to {{name=&quot;&quot;, value = &quot;&quot;}}, then the environment from the parent process is used. If environmental variables are set with the parameter, the parent values may not be passed to the process. To view the current environment, use the &quot;env&quot; command.&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:directory" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The directory in which to execute the command. The default value of this parameter $CWD, which represents the user's current working or home directory. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:throwExceptionOnNonZeroReturn" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then throw an exception if the subprocess returns non-zero.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If a positive integer, then it is the maximum number of times to execute the actor.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:prependPlatformDependentShellCommand" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;If true, then prepend the platform dependent shell command to the&#10;parsed value of the command parameter.  By setting this argument&#10;to true, it is possible to invoke commands in a platform neutral&#10;method.&#10;&lt;p&gt;Under Windows NT or XP, the arguments &quot;cmd.exe&quot; and &quot;/C&quot; are&#10;prepended.  Under Windows 95, the arguments &quot;command.com&quot; and &quot;/C&quot;&#10;are prepended.  Under all other platforms, the arguments &quot;/bin/sh&quot;&#10;and &quot;-c&quot; are prepended. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The default value of this parameter is a boolean of value false,&#10;which allows the user to arbitrarily invoke /bin/sh scripts on all&#10;platforms. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; This must be true if file redirection is used in &lt;i&gt;command&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; Under Cygwin, if true, the path environment of the subprocess is not&#10;identical to the path of the calling process. In this case the full path to the program&#10;must be specified.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="prop:waitForProcess" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then actor will wait until subprocess completes.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:command" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The command to be executed (e.g., echo &quot;Hello, world.&quot;). The command can be specified via either the command port or parameter.</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:44832:776:54">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.Exec">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:976:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#ExternalExecutionEnvironmentActor">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#UnixCommand">
        </property>
        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[325.0, 220.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:102:1:urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:43117:61:114">
        </property>
        <port name="output" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="trigger" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="multiport"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="command" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="error" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="input" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="exitCode" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
        </port>
    </entity>
    <entity name="inp mod" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedCompositeActor">
        <property name="_createdBy" class="ptolemy.kernel.attributes.VersionAttribute" value="9.1.devel">
        </property>
        <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:255:30">
        </property>
        <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.TypedCompositeActor">
            <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:449:1">
            </property>
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#Actor">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#GeneralPurpose">
        </property>
        <property name="semanticType22" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#Workflow">
        </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Yuhong Xiong</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;A Composite actor is an aggregation of actors. It may have a local director that is responsible for executing the contained actors. A Composite actor with a local director is called an opaque actor. Composite actors do not require a local director. Composite actors with no local director &quot;inherit&quot; the director from the containing workflow and are called non-opaque.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;To create a composite actor, drag and drop the Composite actor onto the Workflow canvas. Right-click the actor and select Open Actor from the drop-down menu. A new Kepler application window will open for designing the composite.&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
</property>        <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[450.0, 280.0]">
        </property>
        <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:449:1">
        </property>
        <port name="port" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="input"/>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[125.0, 370.0]">
            </property>
        </port>
        <port name="port2" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
            <property name="output"/>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="[1115.0, 670.0]">
            </property>
        </port>
        <entity name="Expression" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.Expression">
            <property name="expression" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="d + &quot;/&quot; + l + &quot;.inp&quot;">
                <property name="_hide" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Xiaojun Liu, Edward A. Lee, Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The Expression actor evaluates a specified expression (e.g., an addition or multiplication operation), which may reference the values of user-specified input ports, the current time, or the actor's iteration count. The actor outputs the value of the evaluated expression. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Expressions are specified in the Ptolemy expression language via the expression parameter. For more information about the expression language, see http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/papers/05/ptIIdesign1-intro/ptIIdesign1-intro.pdf. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;By default, the expression parameter is empty, and attempting to execute the actor without first specifying an expression generates an error. Expressions can refer to the values of inputs by the port name; to the current time by the identifier &quot;time&quot;; and to the current iteration count by the identifier &quot;iteration.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Input ports are created by the user and correspond to variables used in the specified expression. Currently, the Expression actor does not support input multiports. The actor requires all of its inputs to be present. If inputs are not all present, then the actor will generate an error. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Note: the Expression actor can be used instead of many of the arithmetic actors, such as AddSubtract, MultiplyDivide, and TrigFunction. However, those actors will be usually be more efficient, and sometimes more convenient to use.&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the value of the evaluated expression. The actor automatically determines the type based on the type of the input.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:expression" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An expression to evaluate. Expressions are specified in the Ptolemy expression language. For more information about the expression language, see http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/papers/05/ptIIdesign1-intro/ptIIdesign1-intro.pdf. By default, the parameter is empty, and attempting to execute the actor without first specifying an expression generates an error. Expressions can refer to the values of inputs by the port name; to the current time by the identifier &quot;time&quot;; and to the current iteration count by the identifier &quot;iteration.&quot;</configure></property>
</property>            <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:69:1">
            </property>
            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.Expression">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:950:1">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#MathOperationActor">
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#GeneralPurpose">
            </property>
            <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.BoxedValueIcon">
                <property name="attributeName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="expression">
                </property>
                <property name="displayWidth" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="60">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{160.00000000000009, 423.9687499999998}">
            </property>
            <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:75:1">
            </property>
        </entity>
        <entity name="File Reader" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.io.FileReader">
            <property name="NONE" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="0">
            </property>
            <property name="fileOrURL" class="ptolemy.data.expr.FileParameter" value="/home/pieong/Desktop/git/workflows-master/LigandParameterizationSerial/input/DM0.inp">
            </property>
            <property name="newline" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="property(&quot;line.separator&quot;)">
            </property>
            <property name="firingCountLimit" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="NONE">
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>none</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>yang zhao, edward lee</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>none</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The FileReader actor reads a local file or URL and outputs the contents of the file as a single string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The actor is similar to the SimpleFileReader, except that the FileReader has an additional trigger port and can read a URL via either an input port or parameter.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Kepler contains several actors used to read and output files in different ways. To output each line of the file as a separate string, use the LineReader actor. To output a specified section of the file, use the SegmentFileReader.&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the contents of the file as a single string.</configure></property>
<property name="port:endOfFile" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that indicates whether or not the end of the file has been reached. If the end of the file has been reached, the port will produce a true value. Otherwise, the value is false.</configure></property>
<property name="port:trigger" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A multiport that has no declared type (in other words, the port can accept any data type: double, int, array, etc.) If the port is connected, the actor will not fire until the trigger port receives an input token. Connecting the port is optional, but useful when scheduling the actor to perform at a certain time.</configure></property>
<property name="port:fileOrURL" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An optional input port that accepts the name or URL of a file to be read. When the port is connected, the actor reads the file sent by the previous workflow step. The file name or URL can also be specified using the fileOrURL parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:newline" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The end of line character(s). In general, this setting can be left at its default setting. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:fileOrURL" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The file name or URL of the file to be read. See FileParameter for more information about specifying file names.</configure></property>
</property>            <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:194:1">
            </property>
            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.io.FileReader">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:1045:1">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#ReaderExternalInputActor">
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#LocalInput">
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{330.0000000000001, 358.9687499999998}">
            </property>
            <port name="trigger" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="multiport"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
            <port name="fileOrURL" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
        </entity>
        <entity name="StringSplit" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.string.StringSplit">
            <property name="separator" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="--Link1--\n">
            </property>
            <property name="trimSpaces" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Edward A. Lee</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>$Id: StringSplit.java 61458 2011-07-11 19:54:07Z cxh $</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&#10;This actor reads an input string and splits it into an array of&#10; strings. The &lt;i&gt;separator&lt;/i&gt; parameter is a regular expression&#10; that determines where the split should occur. The default behavior&#10; will split the input at newline characters.</configure></property>
<property name="port:input" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The input port.  This base class imposes no type constraints except  that the type of the input cannot be greater than the type of the  output.</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The output port. By default, the type of this output is constrained  to be at least that of the input.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:separator" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A specification of the separator used to split the string.  The default is &quot;\n&quot;, which results in splitting the string  at newline characters.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:trimSpaces" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>If true, then trim spaces around each resulting string.  This is a boolean that defaults to true.</configure></property>
</property>            <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:162:13">
            </property>
            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.string.StringSplit">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="null">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#DataStringOperation">
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{435.0000000000001, 363.9687499999998}">
            </property>
            <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:678:1">
            </property>
            <property name="" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.DocAttribute">
                <property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="&#10;This actor reads an input string and splits it into an array of&#10; strings. The &lt;i&gt;separator&lt;/i&gt; parameter is a regular expression&#10; that determines where the split should occur. The default behavior&#10; will split the input at newline characters.">
                </property>
                <property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="Edward A. Lee">
                </property>
                <property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="$Id: StringSplit.java 61458 2011-07-11 19:54:07Z cxh $">
                </property>
                <property name="separator (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="A specification of the separator used to split the string.  The default is &quot;\n&quot;, which results in splitting the string  at newline characters.">
                </property>
                <property name="trimSpaces (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="If true, then trim spaces around each resulting string.  This is a boolean that defaults to true.">
                </property>
                <property name="input (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="The input port.  This base class imposes no type constraints except  that the type of the input cannot be greater than the type of the  output.">
                </property>
                <property name="output (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="The output port. By default, the type of this output is constrained  to be at least that of the input.">
                </property>
            </property>
        </entity>
        <entity name="Array To Sequence" class="ptolemy.domains.sdf.lib.ArrayToSequence">
            <property name="arrayLength" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="2">
            </property>
            <property name="enforceArrayLength" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>unknown</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The ArrayToSequence actor  outputs the individual values of an array as a sequence of tokens.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The actor can accept an array with any element type (e.g., int, double, etc.). Each time the actor fires, it reads and disassembles one array and outputs a sequence of values.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The arrayLength parameter can be used to specify the length of the source array. If the enforceArrayLength parameter is selected, then the actor will only accept arrays of the specified length. The enforceArrayLength parameter should be selected if using an SDF director. If using other directors, such as DE or PN, the enforceArrayLength parameter can be deselected, in which case the arrayLength parameter is ignored.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The ArrayToSequence actor is similar to the ArrayToElements actor, except that it outputs values as a sequence via a single output port. The ArrayToElements actor outputs individual values on multiple channels of the output port. Use the ArrayAccumulator actor to convert an array into a single string, where each value is separated by a specified separator.&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
<property name="port:input" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An input port that accepts an array of elements of any type.</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts a sequence of the disassembled array values. </configure></property>
<property name="prop:enforceArrayLength" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether or not to enforce the arrayLength parameter. By default, the arrayLength is enforced, and the actor will only accept arrays of the specified length.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:arrayLength" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The size of the input array. The default is 1.</configure></property>
</property>            <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:175:9">
            </property>
            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.domains.sdf.lib.ArrayToSequence">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:907:1">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#ArrayActor">
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#DataArrayOperation">
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{565.0000000000001, 368.9687499999998}">
            </property>
            <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:31:1">
            </property>
        </entity>
        <entity name="Expression2" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.Expression">
            <property name="expression" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value=" &quot;\n%nproc=&quot; + n + &quot;\n%mem=&quot; + m + &quot;gb\n&quot; + input">
                <property name="_hide" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Xiaojun Liu, Edward A. Lee, Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The Expression actor evaluates a specified expression (e.g., an addition or multiplication operation), which may reference the values of user-specified input ports, the current time, or the actor's iteration count. The actor outputs the value of the evaluated expression. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Expressions are specified in the Ptolemy expression language via the expression parameter. For more information about the expression language, see http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/papers/05/ptIIdesign1-intro/ptIIdesign1-intro.pdf. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;By default, the expression parameter is empty, and attempting to execute the actor without first specifying an expression generates an error. Expressions can refer to the values of inputs by the port name; to the current time by the identifier &quot;time&quot;; and to the current iteration count by the identifier &quot;iteration.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Input ports are created by the user and correspond to variables used in the specified expression. Currently, the Expression actor does not support input multiports. The actor requires all of its inputs to be present. If inputs are not all present, then the actor will generate an error. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Note: the Expression actor can be used instead of many of the arithmetic actors, such as AddSubtract, MultiplyDivide, and TrigFunction. However, those actors will be usually be more efficient, and sometimes more convenient to use.&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the value of the evaluated expression. The actor automatically determines the type based on the type of the input.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:expression" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An expression to evaluate. Expressions are specified in the Ptolemy expression language. For more information about the expression language, see http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/papers/05/ptIIdesign1-intro/ptIIdesign1-intro.pdf. By default, the parameter is empty, and attempting to execute the actor without first specifying an expression generates an error. Expressions can refer to the values of inputs by the port name; to the current time by the identifier &quot;time&quot;; and to the current iteration count by the identifier &quot;iteration.&quot;</configure></property>
</property>            <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:218:4">
            </property>
            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.Expression">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:950:1">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#MathOperationActor">
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#GeneralPurpose">
            </property>
            <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.BoxedValueIcon">
                <property name="attributeName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="expression">
                </property>
                <property name="displayWidth" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="60">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{485.0000000000001, 493.9687499999998}">
            </property>
            <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:75:1">
            </property>
            <port name="input" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
                <property name="input"/>
            </port>
        </entity>
        <entity name="String Replace" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.string.StringReplace">
            <property name="pattern" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="\n%nproc=4\n%mem=40gb\n">
            </property>
            <property name="replacement" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="--Link1--">
            </property>
            <property name="stringToEdit" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="&#10;%nproc=12&#10;%mem=96gb&#10;%chk=molecule&#10;#HF/6-31G* SCF=tight Test Pop=MK iop(6/33=2) iop(6/42=6) opt&#10;# iop(6/50=1)&#10;&#10;remark line goes here&#10;&#10;0   1&#10;    O   -2.6970000000       -2.2420000000       -0.8490000000     &#10;    N   -2.2940000000        1.1680000000        0.4250000000     &#10;    C   -2.1370000000        0.1520000000       -0.6250000000     &#10;    C   -0.7150000000        0.2140000000       -1.1870000000     &#10;    C    0.2910000000        0.0090000000       -0.0530000000     &#10;    C    1.7070000000       -0.0320000000       -0.6290000000     &#10;    C    2.7140000000       -0.2370000000        0.5050000000     &#10;    N    4.0740000000       -0.2770000000       -0.0480000000     &#10;    C    4.4490000000        1.0250000000       -0.6170000000     &#10;    C    5.0430000000       -0.7070000000        0.9680000000     &#10;    C   -2.3870000000       -1.2150000000       -0.0420000000     &#10;    O   -2.3090000000       -1.3870000000        1.1520000000     &#10;    C   -1.9060000000        2.4970000000       -0.0670000000     &#10;    C   -3.6680000000        1.1790000000        0.9450000000     &#10;    H   -2.8530000000        0.3420000000       -1.4240000000     &#10;    H   -0.5860000000       -0.5680000000       -1.9340000000     &#10;    H   -0.5490000000        1.1880000000       -1.6480000000     &#10;    H    0.2110000000        0.8320000000        0.6570000000     &#10;    H    0.0780000000       -0.9310000000        0.4560000000     &#10;    H    1.7870000000       -0.8550000000       -1.3390000000     &#10;    H    1.9200000000        0.9080000000       -1.1380000000     &#10;    H    2.6340000000        0.5860000000        1.2150000000     &#10;    H    2.5010000000       -1.1780000000        1.0140000000     &#10;    H    4.4110000000        1.7860000000        0.1620000000     &#10;    H    5.4600000000        0.9670000000       -1.0190000000     &#10;    H    3.7540000000        1.2860000000       -1.4150000000     &#10;    H    4.7810000000       -1.7040000000        1.3220000000     &#10;    H    6.0420000000       -0.7270000000        0.5320000000     &#10;    H    5.0270000000       -0.0080000000        1.8050000000     &#10;    H   -2.5360000000        2.7690000000       -0.9140000000     &#10;    H   -2.0320000000        3.2300000000        0.7300000000     &#10;    H   -0.8630000000        2.4770000000       -0.3820000000     &#10;    H   -3.8700000000        0.2380000000        1.4560000000     &#10;    H   -3.7830000000        2.0060000000        1.6460000000     &#10;    H   -4.3680000000        1.3030000000        0.1190000000     &#10;    H   -2.8490000000       -3.1000000000       -0.4280000000     &#10;&#10;DM0.gesp&#10;&#10;DM0.gesp&#10;&#10;&#10;">
            </property>
            <property name="replaceAll" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
            <property name="regularExpression" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure> Antonio Yordan-Nones, Neil E. Turner, Edward A. Lee</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The StringReplace actor reads a string and searches it for a specified pattern. The actor replaces either the first instance of the pattern or all occurrences of the pattern with a specified replacement string. The actor outputs the edited string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The actor accepts a source string, a replacement string, and a pattern to search for via either its input ports or its parameters. The pattern is specified as a regular expression. For more information about regular expressions, see http://java.sun.com/docs/books/tutorial/extra/regex/index.html.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;If  the replaceAll parameter is specified, the actor will replace all instances of the string that match the specified pattern. Otherwise, the actor will replace only the first instance that matches. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;If the actor finds no match, then the actor outputs the original source string, unchanged.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:stringToEdit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A port that accepts a source string. The actor will edit the string according to the settings specified by the pattern, replacement, and replaceAll parameters.The source string may also be specified with the stringToEdit parameter</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the edited string. </configure></property>
<property name="port:replacement" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A port accepts a replacement string that replaces any matched instance of the specified pattern. The default is an empty string. The replacement string may also be specified via the replacement parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="port:pattern" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A port that accepts a regular expression, which is compared to the input string. The default is an empty string. The regular expression may also be specified via the pattern parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:replaceAll" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether or not to replace all instances that match the pattern. By default, the actor will replace all instances. Deselect the parameter to replace only the first instance.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:stringToEdit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A source string. The actor will edit the string based on the settings specified by the pattern, replacement, and replaceAll parameters. The source string may  be specified via either the stringToEdit port or parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:replacement" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A replacement string that replaces any matched instance of the specified pattern. The default is an empty string. The replacement string may  be specified via either the replacement port or parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:pattern" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A regular expression, which is compared to the input string. The default is an empty string. The regular expression may  be specified via either the pattern port or parameter.</configure></property>
</property>            <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:235:12">
            </property>
            <property name="" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.DocAttribute">
                <property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="&lt;p&gt;The StringReplace actor reads a string and searches it for a specified pattern. The actor replaces either the first instance of the pattern or all occurrences of the pattern with a specified replacement string. The actor outputs the edited string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The actor accepts a source string, a replacement string, and a pattern to search for via either its input ports or its parameters. The pattern is specified as a regular expression. For more information about regular expressions, see http://java.sun.com/docs/books/tutorial/extra/regex/index.html.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;If  the replaceAll parameter is specified, the actor will replace all instances of the string that match the specified pattern. Otherwise, the actor will replace only the first instance that matches. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;If the actor finds no match, then the actor outputs the original source string, unchanged.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;">
                </property>
                <property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value=" Antonio Yordan-Nones, Neil E. Turner, Edward A. Lee">
                </property>
                <property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="null">
                </property>
                <property name="replaceAll (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="Specify whether or not to replace all instances that match the pattern. By default, the actor will replace all instances. Deselect the parameter to replace only the first instance.">
                </property>
                <property name="output (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="An output port that broadcasts the edited string. ">
                </property>
                <property name="stringToEdit (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="A port that accepts a source string. The actor will edit the string according to the settings specified by the pattern, replacement, and replaceAll parameters.The source string may also be specified with the stringToEdit parameter">
                </property>
                <property name="replacement (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="A port accepts a replacement string that replaces any matched instance of the specified pattern. The default is an empty string. The replacement string may also be specified via the replacement parameter.">
                </property>
                <property name="pattern (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="A port that accepts a regular expression, which is compared to the input string. The default is an empty string. The regular expression may also be specified via the pattern parameter.">
                </property>
                <property name="stringToEdit (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="A source string. The actor will edit the string based on the settings specified by the pattern, replacement, and replaceAll parameters. The source string may  be specified via either the stringToEdit port or parameter.">
                </property>
                <property name="replacement (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="A replacement string that replaces any matched instance of the specified pattern. The default is an empty string. The replacement string may  be specified via either the replacement port or parameter.">
                </property>
                <property name="pattern (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="A regular expression, which is compared to the input string. The default is an empty string. The regular expression may  be specified via either the pattern port or parameter.">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.string.StringReplace">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:972:1">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#StringFunctionActor">
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#DataStringOperation">
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{755.0000000000001, 528.9687499999998}">
            </property>
            <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:98:1">
            </property>
            <port name="pattern" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
            <port name="replacement" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
            <port name="stringToEdit" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
        </entity>
        <entity name="String Replace2" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.string.StringReplace">
            <property name="pattern" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="--Link1--%chk=molecule">
            </property>
            <property name="replacement" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="%nproc=12&#10;%mem=96gb&#10;%chk=molecule">
            </property>
            <property name="stringToEdit" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.PortParameter" value="&#10;%nproc=12&#10;%mem=96gb&#10;%chk=molecule&#10;#HF/6-31G* SCF=tight Test Pop=MK iop(6/33=2) iop(6/42=6) opt&#10;# iop(6/50=1)&#10;&#10;remark line goes here&#10;&#10;0   1&#10;    O   -2.6970000000       -2.2420000000       -0.8490000000     &#10;    N   -2.2940000000        1.1680000000        0.4250000000     &#10;    C   -2.1370000000        0.1520000000       -0.6250000000     &#10;    C   -0.7150000000        0.2140000000       -1.1870000000     &#10;    C    0.2910000000        0.0090000000       -0.0530000000     &#10;    C    1.7070000000       -0.0320000000       -0.6290000000     &#10;    C    2.7140000000       -0.2370000000        0.5050000000     &#10;    N    4.0740000000       -0.2770000000       -0.0480000000     &#10;    C    4.4490000000        1.0250000000       -0.6170000000     &#10;    C    5.0430000000       -0.7070000000        0.9680000000     &#10;    C   -2.3870000000       -1.2150000000       -0.0420000000     &#10;    O   -2.3090000000       -1.3870000000        1.1520000000     &#10;    C   -1.9060000000        2.4970000000       -0.0670000000     &#10;    C   -3.6680000000        1.1790000000        0.9450000000     &#10;    H   -2.8530000000        0.3420000000       -1.4240000000     &#10;    H   -0.5860000000       -0.5680000000       -1.9340000000     &#10;    H   -0.5490000000        1.1880000000       -1.6480000000     &#10;    H    0.2110000000        0.8320000000        0.6570000000     &#10;    H    0.0780000000       -0.9310000000        0.4560000000     &#10;    H    1.7870000000       -0.8550000000       -1.3390000000     &#10;    H    1.9200000000        0.9080000000       -1.1380000000     &#10;    H    2.6340000000        0.5860000000        1.2150000000     &#10;    H    2.5010000000       -1.1780000000        1.0140000000     &#10;    H    4.4110000000        1.7860000000        0.1620000000     &#10;    H    5.4600000000        0.9670000000       -1.0190000000     &#10;    H    3.7540000000        1.2860000000       -1.4150000000     &#10;    H    4.7810000000       -1.7040000000        1.3220000000     &#10;    H    6.0420000000       -0.7270000000        0.5320000000     &#10;    H    5.0270000000       -0.0080000000        1.8050000000     &#10;    H   -2.5360000000        2.7690000000       -0.9140000000     &#10;    H   -2.0320000000        3.2300000000        0.7300000000     &#10;    H   -0.8630000000        2.4770000000       -0.3820000000     &#10;    H   -3.8700000000        0.2380000000        1.4560000000     &#10;    H   -3.7830000000        2.0060000000        1.6460000000     &#10;    H   -4.3680000000        1.3030000000        0.1190000000     &#10;    H   -2.8490000000       -3.1000000000       -0.4280000000     &#10;&#10;DM0.gesp&#10;&#10;DM0.gesp&#10;&#10;&#10;">
            </property>
            <property name="replaceAll" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
            <property name="regularExpression" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure> Antonio Yordan-Nones, Neil E. Turner, Edward A. Lee</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The StringReplace actor reads a string and searches it for a specified pattern. The actor replaces either the first instance of the pattern or all occurrences of the pattern with a specified replacement string. The actor outputs the edited string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The actor accepts a source string, a replacement string, and a pattern to search for via either its input ports or its parameters. The pattern is specified as a regular expression. For more information about regular expressions, see http://java.sun.com/docs/books/tutorial/extra/regex/index.html.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;If  the replaceAll parameter is specified, the actor will replace all instances of the string that match the specified pattern. Otherwise, the actor will replace only the first instance that matches. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;If the actor finds no match, then the actor outputs the original source string, unchanged.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the edited string. </configure></property>
<property name="port:stringToEdit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A port that accepts a source string. The actor will edit the string according to the settings specified by the pattern, replacement, and replaceAll parameters.The source string may also be specified with the stringToEdit parameter</configure></property>
<property name="port:replacement" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A port accepts a replacement string that replaces any matched instance of the specified pattern. The default is an empty string. The replacement string may also be specified via the replacement parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="port:pattern" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A port that accepts a regular expression, which is compared to the input string. The default is an empty string. The regular expression may also be specified via the pattern parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:replaceAll" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether or not to replace all instances that match the pattern. By default, the actor will replace all instances. Deselect the parameter to replace only the first instance.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:stringToEdit" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A source string. The actor will edit the string based on the settings specified by the pattern, replacement, and replaceAll parameters. The source string may  be specified via either the stringToEdit port or parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:replacement" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A replacement string that replaces any matched instance of the specified pattern. The default is an empty string. The replacement string may  be specified via either the replacement port or parameter.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:pattern" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>A regular expression, which is compared to the input string. The default is an empty string. The regular expression may  be specified via either the pattern port or parameter.</configure></property>
</property>            <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:235:17">
            </property>
            <property name="" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.DocAttribute">
                <property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="&lt;p&gt;The StringReplace actor reads a string and searches it for a specified pattern. The actor replaces either the first instance of the pattern or all occurrences of the pattern with a specified replacement string. The actor outputs the edited string.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The actor accepts a source string, a replacement string, and a pattern to search for via either its input ports or its parameters. The pattern is specified as a regular expression. For more information about regular expressions, see http://java.sun.com/docs/books/tutorial/extra/regex/index.html.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;If  the replaceAll parameter is specified, the actor will replace all instances of the string that match the specified pattern. Otherwise, the actor will replace only the first instance that matches. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;If the actor finds no match, then the actor outputs the original source string, unchanged.&lt;/p&gt; &#10;">
                </property>
                <property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value=" Antonio Yordan-Nones, Neil E. Turner, Edward A. Lee">
                </property>
                <property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="null">
                </property>
                <property name="replaceAll (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="Specify whether or not to replace all instances that match the pattern. By default, the actor will replace all instances. Deselect the parameter to replace only the first instance.">
                </property>
                <property name="output (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="An output port that broadcasts the edited string. ">
                </property>
                <property name="stringToEdit (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="A port that accepts a source string. The actor will edit the string according to the settings specified by the pattern, replacement, and replaceAll parameters.The source string may also be specified with the stringToEdit parameter">
                </property>
                <property name="replacement (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="A port accepts a replacement string that replaces any matched instance of the specified pattern. The default is an empty string. The replacement string may also be specified via the replacement parameter.">
                </property>
                <property name="pattern (port)" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="A port that accepts a regular expression, which is compared to the input string. The default is an empty string. The regular expression may also be specified via the pattern parameter.">
                </property>
                <property name="stringToEdit (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="A source string. The actor will edit the string based on the settings specified by the pattern, replacement, and replaceAll parameters. The source string may  be specified via either the stringToEdit port or parameter.">
                </property>
                <property name="replacement (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="A replacement string that replaces any matched instance of the specified pattern. The default is an empty string. The replacement string may  be specified via either the replacement port or parameter.">
                </property>
                <property name="pattern (parameter)" class="ptolemy.data.expr.StringParameter" value="A regular expression, which is compared to the input string. The default is an empty string. The regular expression may  be specified via either the pattern port or parameter.">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.string.StringReplace">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:972:1">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#StringFunctionActor">
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#DataStringOperation">
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{880.0000000000001, 598.9687499999998}">
            </property>
            <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:98:1">
            </property>
            <port name="pattern" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
            <port name="replacement" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
            <port name="stringToEdit" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
        </entity>
        <entity name="Expression3" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.Expression">
            <property name="expression" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="&quot;%nproc=&quot; + n + &quot;\n%mem=&quot; + m + &quot;gb\n%chk=molecule&quot;">
                <property name="_hide" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Xiaojun Liu, Edward A. Lee, Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The Expression actor evaluates a specified expression (e.g., an addition or multiplication operation), which may reference the values of user-specified input ports, the current time, or the actor's iteration count. The actor outputs the value of the evaluated expression. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Expressions are specified in the Ptolemy expression language via the expression parameter. For more information about the expression language, see http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/papers/05/ptIIdesign1-intro/ptIIdesign1-intro.pdf. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;By default, the expression parameter is empty, and attempting to execute the actor without first specifying an expression generates an error. Expressions can refer to the values of inputs by the port name; to the current time by the identifier &quot;time&quot;; and to the current iteration count by the identifier &quot;iteration.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Input ports are created by the user and correspond to variables used in the specified expression. Currently, the Expression actor does not support input multiports. The actor requires all of its inputs to be present. If inputs are not all present, then the actor will generate an error. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Note: the Expression actor can be used instead of many of the arithmetic actors, such as AddSubtract, MultiplyDivide, and TrigFunction. However, those actors will be usually be more efficient, and sometimes more convenient to use.&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the value of the evaluated expression. The actor automatically determines the type based on the type of the input.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:expression" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An expression to evaluate. Expressions are specified in the Ptolemy expression language. For more information about the expression language, see http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/papers/05/ptIIdesign1-intro/ptIIdesign1-intro.pdf. By default, the parameter is empty, and attempting to execute the actor without first specifying an expression generates an error. Expressions can refer to the values of inputs by the port name; to the current time by the identifier &quot;time&quot;; and to the current iteration count by the identifier &quot;iteration.&quot;</configure></property>
</property>            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.Expression">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:950:1">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#MathOperationActor">
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#GeneralPurpose">
            </property>
            <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.BoxedValueIcon">
                <property name="attributeName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="expression">
                </property>
                <property name="displayWidth" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="60">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{590.0000000000001, 603.9687499999998}">
            </property>
        </entity>
        <entity name="File Writer" class="org.geon.FileWrite">
            <property name="fileName" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.FilePortParameter" value="/home/pieong/Desktop/git/workflows-master/LigandParameterizationSerial/input/DM0.inp">
            </property>
            <property name="append" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
            </property>
            <property name="confirmOverwrite" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="false">
            </property>
            <property name="alwaysFlush" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>No author given</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The FileWriter actor reads a string and writes it to a file. The actor outputs the file path of the generated file.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Specify a destination file path with the fileName parameter. If the specified file does not exist, then the actor will create it.  If the file already exists, then the actor will ask for permission to overwrite it (unless the append parameter is selected, in which case the new content is appended to the existing content).&lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;The actor is similar to the LineWriter, except that the FileWriter outputs the generated file path, while the LineWriter actor does not. FileWriter is also similar to TextFileWriter, except that the FileWriter actor adds line breaks, while the TextFileWriter does not.&lt;/p&gt;&#10;</configure></property>
<property name="port:input" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An input port that receives a string to write to a file.</configure></property>
<property name="port:url" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the file name of the generated file.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:append" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether to append the input string to an existing, specified file. By default, the actor will overwrite any preexisting file.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:confirmOverwrite" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Specify whether the actor should confirm before overwriting an existing file. By default, the actor will ask for confirmation.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:fileName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>The name of the file to which to write. See FileParameter for more information about specifying file names. </configure></property>
</property>            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="org.geon.FileWrite">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:1003:1">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#WriterOutputActor">
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#LocalOutput">
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{1004.4375000000001, 641.3749999999998}">
            </property>
            <port name="input" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIOPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="multiport"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
            <port name="fileName" class="ptolemy.actor.parameters.ParameterPort">
                <property name="input"/>
                <property name="_showName" class="ptolemy.data.expr.SingletonParameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </port>
        </entity>
        <entity name="Expression4" class="ptolemy.actor.lib.Expression">
            <property name="expression" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="d + &quot;/&quot; + l + &quot;.inp&quot;">
                <property name="_hide" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="true">
                </property>
            </property>
<property name="KeplerDocumentation" class="ptolemy.vergil.basic.KeplerDocumentationAttribute">
<property name="description" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="author" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>Xiaojun Liu, Edward A. Lee, Steve Neuendorffer</configure></property>
<property name="version" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>null</configure></property>
<property name="userLevelDocumentation" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>&lt;p&gt;The Expression actor evaluates a specified expression (e.g., an addition or multiplication operation), which may reference the values of user-specified input ports, the current time, or the actor's iteration count. The actor outputs the value of the evaluated expression. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Expressions are specified in the Ptolemy expression language via the expression parameter. For more information about the expression language, see http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/papers/05/ptIIdesign1-intro/ptIIdesign1-intro.pdf. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;By default, the expression parameter is empty, and attempting to execute the actor without first specifying an expression generates an error. Expressions can refer to the values of inputs by the port name; to the current time by the identifier &quot;time&quot;; and to the current iteration count by the identifier &quot;iteration.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Input ports are created by the user and correspond to variables used in the specified expression. Currently, the Expression actor does not support input multiports. The actor requires all of its inputs to be present. If inputs are not all present, then the actor will generate an error. &lt;/p&gt;&#10;&#10;&lt;p&gt;Note: the Expression actor can be used instead of many of the arithmetic actors, such as AddSubtract, MultiplyDivide, and TrigFunction. However, those actors will be usually be more efficient, and sometimes more convenient to use.&lt;/p&gt;</configure></property>
<property name="port:output" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An output port that broadcasts the value of the evaluated expression. The actor automatically determines the type based on the type of the input.</configure></property>
<property name="prop:expression" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.ConfigurableAttribute"><configure>An expression to evaluate. Expressions are specified in the Ptolemy expression language. For more information about the expression language, see http://ptolemy.eecs.berkeley.edu/papers/05/ptIIdesign1-intro/ptIIdesign1-intro.pdf. By default, the parameter is empty, and attempting to execute the actor without first specifying an expression generates an error. Expressions can refer to the values of inputs by the port name; to the current time by the identifier &quot;time&quot;; and to the current iteration count by the identifier &quot;iteration.&quot;</configure></property>
</property>            <property name="entityId" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjId" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org/ns/:52894:69:1">
            </property>
            <property name="class" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="ptolemy.actor.lib.Expression">
                <property name="id" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:class:950:1">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType00" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:1:1#MathOperationActor">
            </property>
            <property name="semanticType11" class="org.kepler.sms.SemanticType" value="urn:lsid:localhost:onto:2:1#GeneralPurpose">
            </property>
            <property name="_icon" class="ptolemy.vergil.icon.BoxedValueIcon">
                <property name="attributeName" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.StringAttribute" value="expression">
                </property>
                <property name="displayWidth" class="ptolemy.data.expr.Parameter" value="60">
                </property>
            </property>
            <property name="_location" class="ptolemy.kernel.util.Location" value="{498.8749999999974, 711.8437499999601}">
            </property>
            <property name="derivedFrom" class="org.kepler.moml.NamedObjIdReferralList" value="urn:lsid:kepler-project.org:actor:75:1">
            </property>
        </entity>
        <relation name="relation" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation2" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation4" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation5" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation6" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation7" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation8" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation9" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation10" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation3" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <relation name="relation11" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
        </relation>
        <link port="port" relation="relation3"/>
        <link port="port2" relation="relation11"/>
        <link port="Expression.output" relation="relation"/>
        <link port="File Reader.output" relation="relation5"/>
        <link port="File Reader.trigger" relation="relation3"/>
        <link port="File Reader.fileOrURL" relation="relation"/>
        <link port="StringSplit.input" relation="relation5"/>
        <link port="StringSplit.output" relation="relation2"/>
        <link port="Array To Sequence.input" relation="relation2"/>
        <link port="Array To Sequence.output" relation="relation4"/>
        <link port="Expression2.output" relation="relation6"/>
        <link port="Expression2.input" relation="relation4"/>
        <link port="String Replace.stringToEdit" relation="relation6"/>
        <link port="String Replace.output" relation="relation7"/>
        <link port="String Replace2.replacement" relation="relation8"/>
        <link port="String Replace2.stringToEdit" relation="relation7"/>
        <link port="String Replace2.output" relation="relation9"/>
        <link port="Expression3.output" relation="relation8"/>
        <link port="File Writer.input" relation="relation9"/>
        <link port="File Writer.fileName" relation="relation10"/>
        <link port="File Writer.url" relation="relation11"/>
        <link port="Expression4.output" relation="relation10"/>
    </entity>
    <relation name="relation3" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
    </relation>
    <relation name="relation2" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
    </relation>
    <relation name="relation4" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
    </relation>
    <relation name="relation5" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
    </relation>
    <relation name="relation6" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
    </relation>
    <relation name="relation" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
    </relation>
    <relation name="relation7" class="ptolemy.actor.TypedIORelation">
    </relation>
    <link port="Tleap.input" relation="relation6"/>
    <link port="String Constant.output" relation="relation3"/>
    <link port="String Constant.trigger" relation="relation4"/>
    <link port="File Writer.input" relation="relation3"/>
    <link port="File Writer.url" relation="relation5"/>
    <link port="FRCMOD.output" relation="relation6"/>
    <link port="FRCMOD.input" relation="relation5"/>
    <link port="Gaussian Log File.output" relation="relation2"/>
    <link port="Gaussian Log File.trigger" relation="relation"/>
    <link port="Antechamber2.output" relation="relation4"/>
    <link port="Antechamber2.input" relation="relation2"/>
    <link port="Antechamber1.output" relation="relation7"/>
    <link port="inp mod.port" relation="relation7"/>
    <link port="inp mod.port2" relation="relation"/>
</entity>
